<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AzODN on Arizona Organization Development Network</title>
    <link>https://azodn.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AzODN on Arizona Organization Development Network</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 19:00:58 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://azodn.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Community Organization Development in Action</title>
      <link>https://azodn.org/coda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 21:32:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azodn.org/coda/</guid>
      <description>CODA CODA (Community OD in Action) represents AZODN’s aspirational goal of serving. Focused on the eleemosynary community in the Valley, CODA is a group of organizational development consultants partnering to co-create a more vital and effective community. All services are pro bono.
For our clients in the non-profit sector, frequently constrained by resource limitations, CODA provides consulting help to boards and executive directors with planning organizational change, aligning operations and strategy, board governance and team development support in order to help the organization achieve its goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You</title>
      <link>https://azodn.org/thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 16:43:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azodn.org/thank-you/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attributes</title>
      <link>https://azodn.org/attributes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 22:10:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azodn.org/attributes/</guid>
      <description>Sunny Cactus Arizona Desert by berty on Wallpapers.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join Us</title>
      <link>https://azodn.org/join-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 19:01:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azodn.org/join-us/</guid>
      <description> BECOME A MEMBER Our members are a diverse group of professionals who value meaningful connections, sharing powerful ideas and continued professional development. Internal OD Practitioners Seasoned OD Professionals Business professionals who shape and form organizations and culture Professionals new to OD Students Academics Practitioners in adjacent spaces (L&amp;amp;D, Project Management, Coaching, HR, etc.) OD Curious Consultants ANNUAL MEMBERSHIP PRICES Individuals $ 90 /year Advance notice of upcoming programs and networking opportunities Access to nationally recognized and award-winning presenters Bi-weekly newsletter Discounted rates on some events Members only directory access Partnership with the National OD Network, including access to resource toolkit, newsletters, member rates for events &amp;amp; more JOIN NOW Students $ 50 /year Advance notice of upcoming programs and networking opportunities Access to nationally recognized and award-winning presenters Bi-weekly newsletter Discounted rates on some events Members only directory access Partnership with the National OD Network, including access to resource toolkit, newsletters, member rates for events &amp;amp; more JOIN NOW Corporations $ 250 /year Up to three (3) memberships Advance notice of upcoming programs and networking opportunities Access to nationally recognized and award-winning presenters Bi-weekly newsletter Discounted rates on some events Members only directory access Partnership with the National OD Network, including access to resource toolkit, newsletters, member rates for events &amp;amp; more JOIN NOW </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Reliable Method For Unlocking Potential In Group Experiences</title>
      <link>https://azodn.org/events/a-reliable-method-for-unlocking-potential-in-group-experiences/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 23:25:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azodn.org/events/a-reliable-method-for-unlocking-potential-in-group-experiences/</guid>
      <description>04/20/2023, 11:30 AM – 1:30 PM @ Virtual (Zoom)
Amplify Learning, Create Deeper Connections, and Build Community in your meetings, events, workshops and trainings online and in person.
Jeremy Reisig is the Head Of Admissions for XCHANGE, a facilitation training company dedicated to teaching change agents how to unlock human potential at scale. XCHANGE has been the go-to facilitation method for well-known learning communities, industry-leading corporations, and global community-building initiatives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elements of the Navy&#39;s SEAL Teams That Have Value to Any Organization</title>
      <link>https://azodn.org/events/elements-of-the-navys-seal-teams-that-have-value-to-any-organization/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 17:36:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azodn.org/events/elements-of-the-navys-seal-teams-that-have-value-to-any-organization/</guid>
      <description>Fundamentals: Elements of the Navy&amp;rsquo;s SEAL Teams that have value to any organization
03/07/2023, 6:00 PM – 7:00 PM @ Tempe Public Library
Join us to learn the most impactful ingredients in the Navy’s SEAL Teams that have actionable value for the private sector. Learn how organizations can accelerate their progress toward agility and sustainability by embracing simple constructs and frameworks that promote superior performance amid uncertainty and ambiguity with far-reaching impact and immediate results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Transformation Is More Than Digital Transformation</title>
      <link>https://azodn.org/events/digital-transformation-is-more-than-digital-transformation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 17:33:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azodn.org/events/digital-transformation-is-more-than-digital-transformation/</guid>
      <description>Digital Transformation Is More Than Digital Transformation featuring Mark LaScola and David Casey
01/24/2023, 12:00 PM – 1:30 PM @ Zoom
Join us for a provocative conversation around what digital transformation is and isn’t. In a world full of corporate buzzwords, digital transformation gets thrown around without considering the full impact across an entire organization. Digital transformation doesn’t exist in a vacuum, it requires more than an online platform, and an organization needs to be part of the journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating Complex Problems In A Polarized World</title>
      <link>https://azodn.org/events/navigating-complex-problems-in-a-polarized-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 11:51:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azodn.org/events/navigating-complex-problems-in-a-polarized-world/</guid>
      <description>Constant Contact Event Link Here </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Practices in Post-COVID Return to Work Strategies</title>
      <link>https://azodn.org/events/best-practices-in-post-covid-return-to-work-strategies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 18:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azodn.org/events/best-practices-in-post-covid-return-to-work-strategies/</guid>
      <description>Best Practices in Post-COVID Return to Work Strategies</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Two Sided Coin for Workplace Inclusion</title>
      <link>https://azodn.org/events/a-two-sided-coin-for-workplace-inclusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 17:26:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azodn.org/events/a-two-sided-coin-for-workplace-inclusion/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn to equip leaders and people professionals with tools to Lead Transformational Change in DEI &amp; J</title>
      <link>https://azodn.org/events/learn-to-equip-leaders-and-people-professionals/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 19:07:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azodn.org/events/learn-to-equip-leaders-and-people-professionals/</guid>
      <description>Test Event </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Psychological Safety and Transformation Discussion</title>
      <link>https://azodn.org/events/psychological-safety-and-transformation-discussion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 11:18:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azodn.org/events/psychological-safety-and-transformation-discussion/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://azodn.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azodn.org/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you Are you curious about something? Have a question about our mission?
Please feel free to contact us, info@azodn.org.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://azodn.org/about/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azodn.org/about/faq/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://azodn.org/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azodn.org/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>What personal data we collect and why we collect it Comments When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
Contact forms Cookies If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What We Do</title>
      <link>https://azodn.org/about/what-we-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azodn.org/about/what-we-do/</guid>
      <description>Our Purpose AZODN exists to elevate individuals and organizations to their highest potential.
Our Mission We connect professionals driven to improve organizations by offering transformational OD learning opportunities, resources, networking, and events to support their success.
Our Values CONNECT We create opportunities for our community to connect, collaborate, network and belong. We respect the diversity of our members and guests and promote an environment of inclusion, equity and trust.
Build powerful, meaningful connections Engage with like-minded professionals who are eager to learn and grow Network with others in your field to hear about job opportunities and local workplace trends SHARE We value the ever-curious spirit of our community and design offerings and opportunities to share based on their interests, needs, or recent experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who We Are</title>
      <link>https://azodn.org/about/who-we-are/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://azodn.org/about/who-we-are/</guid>
      <description>About AzODN The Arizona Organization Development Network (AzODN) was founded in 1999 by a dedicated group of OD professionals looking to create opportunities to learn, grow, and share together in the Phoenix area. More than 20 years later, we continue to bring these same values to life with quality programming and opportunities to network.
AZODN is a 501(c)6 nonprofit membership organization led by a volunteer Board of Directors.
From those just investigating the world of OD to those that are seasoned professionals, from the valleys to the mountains of Arizona, all are welcome here!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
