<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AZODN</title>
    <link>https://www.azodn.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on AZODN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 19:00:58 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.azodn.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Community Organization Development in Action</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/coda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 21:32:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/coda/</guid>
      <description>CODA CODA (Community OD in Action) represents AZODN’s aspirational goal of serving. Focused on the eleemosynary community in the Valley, CODA is a group of organizational development consultants partnering to co-create a more vital and effective community. All services are pro bono.
For our clients in the non-profit sector, frequently constrained by resource limitations, CODA provides consulting help to boards and executive directors with planning organizational change, aligning operations and strategy, board governance and team development support in order to help the organization achieve its goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Individual</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/join-us/individual/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 17:07:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/join-us/individual/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 16:43:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/thank-you/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 13:50:45 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tony Robbins in Phoenix</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/events/tony-robbins-in-phoenix/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 11:51:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/events/tony-robbins-in-phoenix/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organizational Development by Dr Jp Pawliw Fry</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/events/organizational-development-by-dr-jp-pawliw-fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 11:18:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/events/organizational-development-by-dr-jp-pawliw-fry/</guid>
      <description>Dr JP Pawliw-Fry in Phoenix Labore in esse amet id voluptate quis excepteur. Cillum in do aliqua incididunt nisi eiusmod. Dolor ullamco velit fugiat minim. Laborum sint tempor quis velit occaecat velit ex officia labore eu tempor. Eiusmod duis ea in voluptate dolore laboris velit elit ipsum aute minim anim esse. Minim incididunt amet laborum quis ex enim qui non cillum adipisicing qui eu cillum. In proident aliquip ea non culpa eu ex nulla anim proident velit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speaker by the Sea</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/events/speaker-by-the-sea/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 11:12:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/events/speaker-by-the-sea/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attributes</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/attributes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 22:10:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/attributes/</guid>
      <description>Sunny Cactus Arizona Desert by berty on Wallpapers.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event1</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/events/event1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 19:07:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/events/event1/</guid>
      <description>Test Event </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>test</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/events/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 16:59:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/events/test/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who We Are</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/about/who-we-are/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 16:56:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/about/who-we-are/</guid>
      <description>About AzODN The Arizona Organization Development Network (AzODN) was founded in 1999 by a dedicated group of OD professionals looking to create opportunities to learn, grow, and share together in the Phoenix area. More than 20 years later, we continue to bring these same values to life with quality programming and opportunities to network.
AZODN is a 501(c)6 nonprofit membership organization led by a volunteer Board of Directors.
From those just investigating the world of OD to those that are seasoned professionals, from the valleys to the mountains of Arizona, all are welcome here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What We Do</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/about/what-we-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 16:44:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/about/what-we-do/</guid>
      <description>Our Purpose AZODN exists to elevate individuals and organizations to their highest potential.
Our Mission We connect professionals driven to improve organizations by offering transformational OD learning opportunities, resources, networking, and events to support their success.
Our Values CONNECT We create opportunities for our community to connect, collaborate, network and belong. We respect the diversity of our members and guests and promote an environment of inclusion, equity and trust.
Build powerful, meaningful connections Engage with like-minded professionals who are eager to learn and grow Network with others in your field to hear about job opportunities and local workplace trends SHARE We value the ever-curious spirit of our community and design offerings and opportunities to share based on their interests, needs, or recent experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you Are you curious about something? Do you have some kind of problem with our products? As am hastily invited settled at limited civilly fortune me. Really spring in extent an by. Judge but built gay party world. Of so am he remember although required. Bachelor unpacked be advanced at. Confined in declared marianne is vicinity.
Please feel free to contact us, our customer service center is working for you 24/7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/about/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/about/faq/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
