<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AZODN</title>
    <link>https://www.azodn.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on AZODN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 19:00:58 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.azodn.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 13:50:45 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tony Robbins in Phoenix</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/events/tony-robbins-in-phoenix/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 11:51:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/events/tony-robbins-in-phoenix/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organizational Development by Dr Jp Pawliw Fry</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/events/organizational-development-by-dr-jp-pawliw-fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 11:18:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/events/organizational-development-by-dr-jp-pawliw-fry/</guid>
      <description>Dr JP Pawliw-Fry in Phoenix Labore in esse amet id voluptate quis excepteur. Cillum in do aliqua incididunt nisi eiusmod. Dolor ullamco velit fugiat minim. Laborum sint tempor quis velit occaecat velit ex officia labore eu tempor. Eiusmod duis ea in voluptate dolore laboris velit elit ipsum aute minim anim esse. Minim incididunt amet laborum quis ex enim qui non cillum adipisicing qui eu cillum. In proident aliquip ea non culpa eu ex nulla anim proident velit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speaker by the Sea</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/events/speaker-by-the-sea/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 11:12:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/events/speaker-by-the-sea/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attributes</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/attributes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 22:10:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/attributes/</guid>
      <description>Sunny Cactus Arizona Desert by berty on Wallpapers.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event1</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/events/event1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 19:07:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/events/event1/</guid>
      <description>Test Event </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join Us</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/join-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 19:01:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/join-us/</guid>
      <description> BECOME A MEMBER Our members are a diverse group of professionals who value meaningful connections, sharing powerful ideas and continued professional development. Internal OD Practitioners Seasoned OD Professionals Business professionals who shape and form organizations and culture Professionals new to OD Students Academics Practitioners in adjacent spaces (L&amp;amp;D, Project Management, Coaching, HR, etc.) OD Curious Consultants ANNUAL MEMBERSHIP PRICES Individuals $90/year Advance notice of upcoming programs and networking opportunities Access to nationally recognized and award-winning presenters Bi-weekly newsletter Discounted rates on some events Members only directory access Partnership with the National OD Network, including access to resource toolkit, newsletters, member rates for events &amp;amp; more JOIN NOW Students $50/year Advance notice of upcoming programs and networking opportunities Access to nationally recognized and award-winning presenters Bi-weekly newsletter Discounted rates on some events Members only directory access Partnership with the National OD Network, including access to resource toolkit, newsletters, member rates for events &amp;amp; more JOIN NOW Corporations $250/year Up to three (3) memberships Advance notice of upcoming programs and networking opportunities Access to nationally recognized and award-winning presenters Bi-weekly newsletter Discounted rates on some events Members only directory access Partnership with the National OD Network, including access to resource toolkit, newsletters, member rates for events &amp;amp; more JOIN NOW </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>test</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/events/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 16:59:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/events/test/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who We Are</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/about/who-we-are/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 16:56:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/about/who-we-are/</guid>
      <description>Meet our Volunteer Board </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What We Do</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/about/what-we-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 16:44:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/about/what-we-do/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you Are you curious about something? Do you have some kind of problem with our products? As am hastily invited settled at limited civilly fortune me. Really spring in extent an by. Judge but built gay party world. Of so am he remember although required. Bachelor unpacked be advanced at. Confined in declared marianne is vicinity.
Please feel free to contact us, our customer service center is working for you 24/7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/about/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/about/faq/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
