<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on AZODN</title>
    <link>https://www.azodn.org/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on AZODN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 16:38:23 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.azodn.org/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/about/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/about/faq/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What We Do</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/about/what-we-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/about/what-we-do/</guid>
      <description>Our Purpose AZODN exists to elevate individuals and organizations to their highest potential.
Our Mission We connect professionals driven to improve organizations by offering transformational OD learning opportunities, resources, networking, and events to support their success.
Our Values CONNECT We create opportunities for our community to connect, collaborate, network and belong. We respect the diversity of our members and guests and promote an environment of inclusion, equity and trust.
Build powerful, meaningful connections Engage with like-minded professionals who are eager to learn and grow Network with others in your field to hear about job opportunities and local workplace trends SHARE We value the ever-curious spirit of our community and design offerings and opportunities to share based on their interests, needs, or recent experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who We Are</title>
      <link>https://www.azodn.org/about/who-we-are/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.azodn.org/about/who-we-are/</guid>
      <description>About AzODN The Arizona Organization Development Network (AzODN) was founded in 1999 by a dedicated group of OD professionals looking to create opportunities to learn, grow, and share together in the Phoenix area. More than 20 years later, we continue to bring these same values to life with quality programming and opportunities to network.
AZODN is a 501(c)6 nonprofit membership organization led by a volunteer Board of Directors.
From those just investigating the world of OD to those that are seasoned professionals, from the valleys to the mountains of Arizona, all are welcome here!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
